and to engage in.
行政長官質詢時間結束。
The fight against graft.
And seven percent involve public bodies.
27% was related to government departments.
一 slight decrease of two per cent, when compared to that of 2016.
主席，在我作為顧問委員會成員的職責下，
Of these corruption complaints, 66% were targeted at the private sector.
子 sector elections and five per cent related to the 2017 chief executive elections.
在2017，ICAC收到2,835非選舉相關的腐敗投訴。
On corruption, I hereby brief members on the ICACNL report 2017 tabled in the council today.
現在舉行立法會例行會議，發言石禮謙議員就香港特別行政區廉政公署二零一七年報向本會發言，石禮謙議員。
The number of pursuable complaints was two hundred one, two one two nine, an increase of seven per cent when compared to last year's figures.
Since inception in 1974, the ICAC has been fighting corruption impartially and professionally with a holistic approach, combining law enforcement, prevention and education.
alongside vigorous enforcement actions, the ICAC has put in place system and rules to eliminate corruption loopholes, as well as reaching out to the community to change the public's attitude from meek tolerance to rejection.
維修。
作為結果。
也亦也亦也
noting that the public has a high and legitimate expectation.
Building management continue to attract the largest number of complaints in the private sector.
反貪腐敗在過去12個月，顯示非常低水平的腐敗在香港。
Taking timely intervention action in appropriate cases to frustrate possible corrupt and bid rigging activities at an early stage.
Of such early intervention, flat owners were made aware of the risks exposed in avoiding contracts, enabling them to take appropriate follow-up action at an early stage where necessary.
In order to maximise the effectiveness of the enforcement action, the ICAC implemented a two-pronged strategy consisting of the traditional approach of investigation with a view to prosecution.
amid global concern for corporate governance and business ethics in recent years, the ICAE assisted listed company to adopt a structured approach to corruption risk management through a three years ethics promotion programme.
Governance and ethical leadership for senior officials, which include briefings for the officials appointed under the political appointment system, heads of department and senior civil servants after the new term of office was on board.
Moreover, a total of 500 complaints under the election ordinance was received. Of these complaints, 47% related to 2016 Legislative Council election, 46% related to 2016 Election Committee sub.
主席，總體腐敗情況是處於可控制範圍。ICAC年度調查2017，由一個獨立研究機構進行，發現99.1%的回應者沒有遇到腐敗。
Besides corruption prevention leaflets, training videos, two kits on building management were updated to deliver anti-corruption messages to flat owners, owners' corporations, relevant parties and organisations involved in building management and.
applicant.
要香港， to fulfil its international obligations.
林建峯議員就廉政公署事宜投訴委。
國際合作是essential in the fight against corruption.
under the United Nations Convention Against Corruption (UNCAC).
但 let's not forget that people in many countries are still suffering because of corruption.
We will continue to render the wholehearted support to ICAC as always, President Assefa Meles.
但會也幫助這些國家建一個水平的場地，為企業，這也會也幫助香港公司。
和經驗在錢 laundering 調查和資產回收、Cloaking 技術和其他 pertinent 問題。
Every recognition Hong Kong receive is a constant reminder to us of the importance of continued effort in fostering propriety culture.
不同 walks of life demonstrate zero tolerance on corruption, in stark contrast to the bad old days when Hong Kong was plagued by corruption.
On the integrity and probity of civil servants and public officers, the ICAC assisted the government departments and public bodies in enhancing internal control through improving their system, practices and procedures, with a view to plucking any loopholes.
That may give rise to corrupt practices, dereliction of duty and abuse of power. Last year, 63 assignment study were completed, and timely advice were provided on 490 occasions to government departments and public bodies. The ICA.
一conference on business ethics for listed company were held in September 2017. Moreover, a tailor-made anti-corruption guide and a new training package, which illustrate common ethical risks, were provided to listed company on all prospective listing.
香港有義務協助其他參與國在發展和實施反貪腐措施。在2017年5月，ICAC舉行了一場國際會議，與海外反貪腐機構分享知識。
ICAC also set up a small unit to provide training service to anti-corruption agencies in countries along the Belt and Road routes within the framework of UNCAC to help UNCAC signatories in their fight against corruption. We will not only enable Hong.
主席和各位議員，貿易是其中一項關鍵支柱，奠定香港的基礎。近年來，香港持續被國際評估為最清潔的城市之一。ICAC年度調查顯示，香港居民對環境的滿意度高於全球平均水平。
作為成員會委員會反貪腐，我理解ICAC會保持其承諾，於反貪腐戰線和維持香港競爭優勢，不管面臨的困難和挑戰。有此，我期望公眾成員。